http://www.fernbankmuseum.org/privacy-policy/

Join Our Team
Fernbank is open daily 10am to 5pm. Online tickets required for Members and Non-Members. Learn what we are doing to keep you safe.
Privacy Policy
Introduction
Fernbank is committed to protecting your privacy. The following policy explains how we collect, use and secure any personal information you provide to us through the use of our website. By using Fernbank's website, you consent to the terms of information collection and use as described below. Should changes be made to the policy, they will be posted here.
Information Collected
Fernbank does not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. We may request and retain personal information about you if you contact us through our website or if you participate in any of our online or broadcast activities; these include, but are not limited to: purchases, subscriptions, registration, requests for museum information, event reservations and charitable donations. Requested information could include your name, email address, postal address and telephone number. When teachers make field trip reservations online, we collect information about the type of school and its location. We do not knowingly collect information from children.
The museum's web server automatically collects some anonymous, non-personally identifiable information for every visitor to our website including the visitor's domain name and Internet Protocol ("IP") address, or the number assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. Additionally, we collect information about our visitors' browsers, Internet Providers and preferred search engines. This information is used for statistical analysis and monitoring system efficiency.
Information Use
Fernbank does not release your personal information to any non-authorized third parties without your permission. Authorized third parties who may receive your information include but are not limited to mailhouses under hire by Fernbank and consultants working on behalf of the museum. Fernbank does not sell its member, donor lists or email subscriber lists and does not share this information with any other entity. Fernbank may share its donor, member or email subscriber list with an authorized third party that is working on behalf of Fernbank.
From time to time, we may conduct market research through statistical analysis of aggregate (non-personally identifiable) information gathered in the methods stated above. Careful collection and analysis of this information can also be applied to measure interests within various components of our site and the overall user-friendliness of the entire site to improve your online experience with Fernbank.
When you send us an email from our site, we may retain information such as the content, your email address, our response, and the text of any follow-up questions you may have. We may use this information, for example, to measure how effectively we address concerns online.
Security of Information
Fernbank protects all personal and non-personally identifiable information received through its website against unauthorized access. In general, security of data transmissions over the Internet cannot be guaranteed. We will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.
Personally identifiable information is only accessible to a limited number of employees who have specific access rights to systems storing such information. All employees are required to follow our security and privacy practices to ensure that your information is protected.
Fernbank cannot guarantee the security, accuracy or completeness of any information or procedures. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personal identity information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Donating or Purchasing Online
When making a contribution, purchasing a membership or event tickets via Fernbank's website, you are automatically redirected to a secure, third-party server to complete the transaction. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with their independent privacy policy as it may differ from our own.
Personal information that is gained through this transaction is used by Fernbank to communicate with you directly about your purchase and the benefits associated with that purchase. Fernbank Museum does not sell its member or donor lists. Fernbank may share its donor/member list with an authorized third party that is working on behalf of Fernbank. If we share this information with third parties, we require them to treat the information in strict confidence and to use it only for the purpose for which it was shared.
Promotional Email
With your permission, we may use any personally identifiable information you submit for museum marketing and promotional purposes. For example, Fernbank may send emails to inform interested parties of current programming or other relevant events.
You will not receive these communications unless you "opt-in" by willingly providing the personal information required. Should you no longer wish to receive such information from us, you may "opt-out" at any time by following the "unsubscribe" directions included with every email message.
Notification of Changes
From time to time, Fernbank may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on the museum's website. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we disclose it.
Fernbank will use information in accordance with this Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. If circumstances arise that relate to disclosure of information about users that is not within the scope of this Privacy Policy, Fernbank will use its judgment in deciding how to process. This Privacy Policy posted on this site was updated on or about July 1, 2019.
Children Under 13
Fernbank does not intentionally solicit or collect personal information about children under the age of 18. If you are under 18 and would like to use this website, please ask a parent or guardian for assistance.
Legal Issues
This is a United States website and is subject to United States law. Fernbank will disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to Fernbank employees or property (including this site), members, visitors, donors or to others.
Contact Information
WebsiteFernbank Museum of Natural History767 Clifton Road, NEAtlanta, Georgia  30307
